(Sheldon:)I'm not asking for me.
(Sheldon:)I'm asking for Hawking.
Let me try gangster: Hells no.
(Sheldon:)Okay, look. How about this?
You just give him my paper
on the Higgs boson.
If he sees the breakthrough l've made,
he'll reach out to me.
- What if he doesn't?
- Yeah, he will. He's really smart.
(Howard:)That's an interesting idea.
(Howard:)Why don't you give me a minute
to talk it over with my friends?
- How?
- Walk away.
Walking away!
(Leonard:)You do realize
you own his ass right now.
(Raj:)l do.
(Raj:)You can make him
do anything you want.
(Howard:)Yeah, I know. I'm just trying to figure out
how much I wanna punish him.
(Raj:)Well, don't be too mean.
Hey, I'm thinking about making...
(Sheldon:)...freshly brewed iced tea
if anyone would like some.